DJORDJE LJUBINKOVIC



SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

+381 63 283 101

□ ljubinkovicdj93@gmail.com

♠ Belgrade, Serbia

in https://linkedin.com/in/ljubinkovicd/

https://github.com/ljubinkovicdj93

SKILLS

iOS (Swift & Objective-C)

Vapor (Swift backend)

С

SQL

LISP

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

University of Findlay, Ohio 2012-2016

AWARDS

Phi Kappa Phi Award - top 7% University of Findlay | Ohio 2012 - 2016

Pi Mu Epsilon Award

University of Findlay | Ohio 2012 - 2016

GLIAC Excellence - GPA > 3.5 University of Findlay | Ohio 2012 - 2016

PROFILE

Results-oriented software developer with 4 years of experience in iOS development.

Focused on creating modular, testable and easily maintainable code. Highly adaptable to quickly changing technical environments

Always striving to improve and learn from others, and willing to share my knowledge and teach others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

LotusFlare | Belgrade, Serbia | September 2019 - Present

Worked on a customer care app called Tapp, for

telecommunication operator Digi, in Malaysia.

The app utilizes CleanSwift architecture.

I've also helped in developing internal modules which are used by this app, and other internal apps. These modules are:

- · Camera controller.
- Form library.
- Networking and storage module, ui toolkit, and various utilities.

Software Engineer

Symphony | Belgrade, Serbia | January 2018 - September 2019 Worked on many different project for various clients.

Some of the projects that I've worked on are:

- React Native app which uses Bluetooth to communicate with custom made hardware.
- iOS app which uses wireless radio frequency signals to detect motion inside home environment.

Software Engineer

Ametek | Mount Prospect, IL, USA | June 2016 - October 2017
Developed apps which were used by both caregivers and patients inside healthcare facilities.

- · Caregiver app to respond to patient app requests.
- Patient app which communicated with the caregiver app using REST endpoints, as well as through SIP (only audio).
- · Designed and in-house SharePoint intranet website.